Class of 1968 Records, 1964-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1968 Records
1964-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1968.
RG 80 UUID:9ceaa21f-6234-4d7c-8e1a-2a591deb93ea
3 boxes (1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1968.
The Class of 1968 was the ninetieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1968 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1968, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1968 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General undated (Box 2244, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1964-1965 (Box 2244, Folder 4)
- Groups 1964-1968 (Box 2244, Folder 5)
- History 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 6)
- Hoop Roll 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1969-1975 (Box 2244, Folder 9)
- Newsletters-"Connections" 1995-2002 (Box 2244, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 2244, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1978-1983 (Box 2244, Folder 12)
- Reunions-Reunion Yearbook 1993 (Box 2244, Folder 13)
- Reunions 2003 (Box 2244, Folder 14)
- Senior Luncheon 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 15)
- Songs 1968 (Box 2244, Folder 16)
- Who's Who 1964 (Box 2244, Folder 17)